

I am a student of business informatics. Software development and computer science play an important role in my daily life, not only at school and at work. My ambitions and goals include making people's lives easier through digital technologies and making a positive impact on the world through my developments. My strengths lie in reliability and efficient, precise work. Thanks to my previous experience and my empathetic way of thinking, I can easily find common ground with my colleagues. My technical skills allow me to work easily with digital systems and software. I find it extremely important that I am constantly working to expand my current knowledge and learn new things.

Márton Simon

Phone number:

+43 664 185 3288

E-mail address:

smarton0614@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/m%C3%A 1rton-simon-5ba59a263/

Github:

https://github.com/farkas1070

Skills

- Python
- Javascript
- Typescript
- HTML, CSS
- ReactJS
- Angular
- MSSQL, MongoDB, MySQL
- React Native
- Node.js
- Firebase
- Photoshop
- .Net Core, C#
- Bootstrap, Taiwlind, Chakra Ui
- Microsoft Excel, Word, Access, PowerBI

Language skills

Hungarian – native English – fluent German – intermediate

Work Experience

06/2023 - 09/2023

Application Developer - Internship

Sopron

Effix Marketing Ltd.

 Participation in a project team with focus on the development of a mobile application

11/2019 - now

Independent contractor - distribution of advertising material (Krone and Kurier daily newspapers)

Frankenau, Großmutschen, kleinmutschen

PDW Logistik GmbH

 My tasks consist of the daily delivery of various written media.

Education

09/2020 - now

Bachelor in Business Informatics

University of Sopron – Sopron

09/2015 - 06/2019

Oberstufe

Jurisich Miklós Grammar School and College - Kőszeg

09/2013 - 06/2015

Grundschule

Árpád-házi Szent Margit elementary school, grammar school and college - Kőszeg

09/2007-06/2013

Grundschule

Gubányi Károly Primary School - Pilis